Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- Committee Records, 1952-2003; 1952 2003; 101.5 linear feet
  - Committee on Lectureships
    - National Lecturers: Wray, Wayne, 1982-1984 (Box 2.185, Folder 1)
    - National Lecturers: Wrighton, Mark S., 1983-1984 (Box 2.185, Folder 2)
    - National Lecturers: Zumberge, James H., 1978-1980 (Box 2.185, Folder 3)
    - National Lectureship Program, 1995 (Box 2.185, Folder 4)
    - National Lecturer Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 2.121, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1973-1992 (Box 2.121, Folder 7)
    - Questionnaires, Centennial, 1987 (Box 2.185, Folder 5)
    - Regional Lecture Reports, 1976 (Box 2.185, Folder 8)
    - Regional Lecturers, 1972 (Box 2.185, Folder 6)
    - Regional Lecturers, 1972-1973 (Box 2.185, Folder 7)
    - Regional Lectureships: Mid-Atlantic, 1981-1982 (Box 2.121, Folder 8)
    - Regional Lectureships: Mid-Atlantic, 1983-1992 (Box 2.121, Folder 9)
    - Regional Lectureships: North Central, 1979-1985 (Box 2.122, Folder 1)
    - Regional Lectureships: North Central, 1987-1990 (Box 2.122, Folder 2)
    - Regional Lectureships: Northeast, 1979-1990 (Box 2.122, Folder 3)
    - Regional Lectureships: Northwest, 1982-1990 (Box 2.122, Folder 4)
    - Regional Lectureships: Southeast, 1980-1989 (Box 2.122, Folder 5)
    - Regional Lectureships: Southwest, 1978-1980 (Box 2.122, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 2.185, Folder 9)
    - Report, 7-9 Oct. 1972 (Box 2.185, Folder 10)
    - Reports to Assembly of Delegates, 1996 (Box 2.185, Folder 11)
    - Reports to Board of Directors, 1974-1989 (Box 2.122, Folder 7)
    - Statistics, 1968-1973 (Box 2.185, Folder 12)
    - Statistics, 1985-1987 (Box 2.122, Folder 8)
    - Statistics, 1987-1988 (Box 2.122, Folder 9)
    - Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 2.122, Folder 10)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 2.122, Folder 11)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 2.123, Folder 1)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 2.123, Folder 2)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 2.123, Folder 3)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 2.123, Folder 4)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 2.123, Folder 5)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 2.123, Folder 6)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2.124, Folder 1)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2.124, Folder 2)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2.124, Folder 3)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2.124, Folder 4)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1994 (Box 2.124, Folder 5)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1994 (Box 2.124, Folder 6)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 2.125, Folder 1)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 2.125, Folder 2)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 2.125, Folder 3)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1998 (Box 2.125, Folder 4)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1998 (Box 2.125, Folder 5)
    - Subsidy Awards, 1995-1998 (Box 2.125, Folder 6)
    - Tour Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 2.185, Folder 13)
    - Unused Lectureship Subsidies, 1992-1993 (Box 2.125, Folder 7)
    - Unused Lectureship Subsidies, 1993-1994 (Box 2.125, Folder 8)
    - Unsubsidized Lectureships, 1993-1994 (Box 2.125, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Long-Range Planning
    - Conference Call, 8 Dec. 1992 (Box 2.126, Folder 1)
    - Conference Call, 12 May 1993 (Box 2.126, Folder 2)
    - General, 1984-1986 (Box 2.185, Folder 14)
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.126, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 13-14 Sep. 1980 (Box 2.126, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 15-16 Mar. 1986 (Box 2.126, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 12-14 Dec. 1986 (Box 2.126, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 4-6 Dec. 1987 (Box 2.126, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 18-19 Mar. 1988 (Box 2.126, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 19 Aug. 1988 (Box 2.126, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 5 Oct. 1996 (Box 2.126, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 18 Aug. 1997 (Box 2.126, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 15 Oct. 1997 (Box 2.127, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 15-16 Jun. 1998 (Box 2.127, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 29 Aug. 2000 (Box 2.127, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 18-19 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.185, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 31 Jan. 1964 (Box 2.185, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 10 Mar. 1964 (Box 2.185, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 17 Feb. 1965 (Box 2.185, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 10 Mar. 1966 (Box 2.185, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 22 Mar. 1968 (Box 2.185, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 23 May 1970 (Box 2.186, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 11 Jan. 1971 (Box 2.186, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 24 May 1972 (Box 2.186, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 8-9 Feb. 1973 (Box 2.186, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 7 May 1973 (Box 2.186, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 9 Jan. 1974 (Box 2.186, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 24 Apr. 1974 (Box 2.186, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 19 Aug. 1974 (Box 2.186, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 3 Feb. 1975 (Box 2.186, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 25 Jun. 1975 (Box 2.186, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 9-10 Oct. 1975 (Box 2.186, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 13-14 Mar. 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 10 Jun. 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 22-23 Aug. 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 22 Oct. 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 5-7 Dec. 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 22 Jul. 1983 (Box 2.186, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 27 Oct. 1983 (Box 2.186, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 6 May 1984 (Box 2.186, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1-3 Mar. 1985 (Box 2.186, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 22-24 Nov. 1985 (Box 2.186, Folder 21)
    - Progress Report, 1989 (Box 2.186, Folder 22)
    - Report to Assembly of Delegates, 1987 (Box 2.186, Folder 23)
    - Report: Croxton, Frank, 9 Dec. 1978 (Box 2.186, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Meetings
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 2.127, Folder 4)
    - Conference Call, 30 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.127, Folder 5)
    - Conference Call, 2 Sep. 1993 (Box 2.127, Folder 6)
    - Conference Call, 6 Jul. 1994 (Box 2.127, Folder 7)
    - General, 1991-1994 (Box 2.127, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 21-25 Jan. 1988 (Box 2.127, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 28 Jan. 1988 (Box 2.127, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 30 Oct. 1988 (Box 2.127, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 27-28 Jan. 1989 (Box 2.127, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, 27-29 Jan. 1989 (Box 2.186, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, 28 Jan. 1989 (Box 2.127, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, 27 Jan. 1990 (Box 2.127, Folder 14)
    - Meeting, 22 Feb. 1991 (Box 2.128, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 3 Oct. 1992 (Box 2.128, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1975 (Box 2.186, Folder 26)
    - Reports, 1976 (Box 2.186, Folder 27)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box 2.186, Folder 28)
    - Reports, 1979 (Box 2.186, Folder 29)
    - Reports, 1981 (Box 2.186, Folder 30)
    - Reports, 1982 (Box 2.186, Folder 31)
    - Reports, 1983 (Box 2.186, Folder 32)
    - Reports, 1984 (Box 2.186, Folder 33)
    - Reports, 1985 (Box 2.187, Folder 1)
    - Response, 1992 (Box 2.128, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Membership
    - Adopt-A-Chapter Project, 1992 (Box 2.187, Folder 2)
    - Analysis of Membership Data, 1988-1992 (Box 2.187, Folder 3)
    - Analysis of Membership Data, 1988-1992 (Box 2.187, Folder 4)
    - Attrition Rate Study, 1995 (Box 2.187, Folder 5)
    - Categorization, 1991-1992 (Box 2.187, Folder 6)
    - Certificate of Recognition for Librarians, 1981-1982 (Box 2.128, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of Recognition for Librarians, 1982-1983 (Box 2.128, Folder 5)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1965-1969 (Box 2.128, Folder 6)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1970 (Box 2.128, Folder 7)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1971-1972 (Box 2.128, Folder 8)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1973-1974 (Box 2.128, Folder 9)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1975 (Box 2.128, Folder 10)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1976 (Box 2.128, Folder 11)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1977 (Box 2.129, Folder 1)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1977 (Box 2.129, Folder 2)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1978 (Box 2.129, Folder 3)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1978 (Box 2.129, Folder 4)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1979 (Box 2.129, Folder 5)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1980-1981 (Box 2.129, Folder 6)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1982-1983 (Box 2.129, Folder 7)
    - Chapter-At-Large Records, 1984 (Box 2.129, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Focus Group, 1994 (Box 2.187, Folder 7)
    - Committee Service, 1993-1994 (Box 2.187, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2.187, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2.187, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2.187, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2.13, Folder 1)
    - "Currently Active" Initiates, 1983 (Box 2.187, Folder 12)
    - Dallas Focus Group, 17 Sep. 1994 (Box 2.187, Folder 13)
    - Delegate Opinion Survey, 1990 (Box 2.188, Folder 1)
    - Dues Increase, 1991 (Box 2.13, Folder 2)
    - Early Bird Registration, 1989 (Box 2.13, Folder 3)
    - General, 1981 (Box 2.188, Folder 2)
    - General, 1985 (Box 2.13, Folder 4)
    - General, 1986 (Box 2.13, Folder 5)
    - General, 1987 (Box 2.13, Folder 6)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 2.13, Folder 7)
    - General, Apr. - May 1990 (Box 2.13, Folder 8)
    - General, Jun. 1990 (Box 2.13, Folder 9)
    - General, Jul. - Aug. 1990 (Box 2.13, Folder 10)
    - General, Sep. - Dec. 1990 (Box 2.13, Folder 11)
    - General, 1991-1994 (Box 2.188, Folder 3)
    - General, Jan. - Mar. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 1)
    - General, Apr. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 2)
    - General, May 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 3)
    - General, Jun. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 4)
    - General, Jul. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 5)
    - General, Aug. - Sep. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 6)
    - General, Oct. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 7)
    - General, Nov. 1991 (Box 2.131, Folder 8)
    - General, Dec. 1991- May 1992 (Box 2.131, Folder 9)
    - General, Jun. - Dec. 1992 (Box 2.131, Folder 10)
    - General, Jan. - Jun. 1993 (Box 2.132, Folder 1)
    - General, Jul. - Oct. 1993 (Box 2.132, Folder 2)
    - General, Nov. 1993 - Jan. 1994 (Box 2.132, Folder 3)
    - General, Feb. - Apr. 1994 (Box 2.132, Folder 4)
    - General, May - Sep. 1994 (Box 2.132, Folder 5)
    - General, Oct. - Dec. 1994 (Box 2.132, Folder 6)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.132, Folder 7)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.132, Folder 8)
    - General, 1997 (Box 2.132, Folder 9)
    - "Health Reports" of Initiations and Promotions, 1981-1992 (Box 2.188, Folder 4)
    - Ideas on Increasing Membership, 1990-1992 (Box 2.188, Folder 5)
    - Interviews, 15 Feb. 1993 (Box 2.132, Folder 10)
    - Initiates: Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Brown University, 1984 (Box 2.188, Folder 6)
    - Initiates: Promotions, 1990-1991 (Box 2.188, Folder 7)
    - Initiate Retention, May 1992 (Box 2.188, Folder 8)
    - Initiate Trends by Category, 1992 (Box 2.188, Folder 9)
    - Initiate Trends by Chapter/Club, 1991-1994 (Box 2.188, Folder 10)
    - Initiate Trends by Chapter/Club, 1991-1994 (Box 2.188, Folder 11)
    - Initiate Trends by Chapter/Club, 1991-1994 (Box 2.188, Folder 12)
    - Largest Groups, 1988 (Box 2.188, Folder 13)
    - Link Between Membership and Grants-In-Aid of Research, 1993-1994 (Box 2.188, Folder 14)
    - Major Research University Information, 1990-1992 (Box 2.188, Folder 15)
    - Major Research Universities Statistics, 1989 (Box 2.188, Folder 16)
    - Marketing Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 2.189, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 17 Apr. 1986 (Box 2.133, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 15-16 Jun. 1990 (Box 2.133, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 5-7 Apr. 1991 (Box 2.133, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, Nov. 1991 (Box 2.133, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, Jan. 1993 (Box 2.133, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 12 Oct. 1993 (Box 2.133, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 14-16 Jan. 1994 (Box 2.133, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, Jan. 1994 (Box 2.133, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, Jan. 1995 (Box 2.133, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, Mar. 1995 (Box 2.133, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 13-15 Jan. 1995 (Box 2.133, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 12-14 Jan. 1996 (Box 2.133, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, 29 Nov. - 1 Dec. 1996 (Box 2.133, Folder 13)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1991 (Box 2.134, Folder 1)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1992 (Box 2.134, Folder 2)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1993 (Box 2.134, Folder 3)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1994 (Box 2.134, Folder 4)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1995 (Box 2.134, Folder 5)
    - National Conference on Undergraduate Research, 1997 (Box 2.134, Folder 6)
    - New Director, 1993-1989 (Box 2.189, Folder 2)
    - "New" Inactives, 1992 (Box 2.189, Folder 3)
    - Non-Dues-Paying Membership Study, 1994 (Box 2.135, Folder 1)
    - Originals of Documents, 1997 (Box 2.189, Folder 4)
    - Perspectives on Membership Report, Dec. 1986 (Box 2.189, Folder 5)
    - Problems, 1989-1990 (Box 2.135, Folder 2)
    - Response, 1992 (Box 2.135, Folder 3)
    - Ritchko, Sue Anne: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2.189, Folder 6)
    - Status Breakdown of Initiates by Date, 1991 (Box 2.189, Folder 7)
    - Status of Affiliates, 1988-1991 (Box 2.189, Folder 8)
    - Total Membership, 1979-1988 (Box 2.189, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Nominations
    - General, 1990-1994 (Box 2.135, Folder 4)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.135, Folder 5)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.135, Folder 6)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.135, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 4-5 Mar. 1988 (Box 2.135, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 10-11 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.135, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 10-12 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.135, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 17-18 Mar. 1990 (Box 2.135, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, Jun. 1992 (Box 2.135, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, 28 Oct. 1993 (Box 2.135, Folder 13)
    - Meeting Planning, 1997 (Box 2.135, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 2.189, Folder 10)
    - Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 2.189, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 2.189, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1975 (Box 2.189, Folder 13)
    - Reports, 1976 (Box 2.189, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1977 (Box 2.189, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box 2.189, Folder 16)
    - Reports, 1979 (Box 2.189, Folder 17)
    - Reports, 1980 (Box 2.189, Folder 18)
    - Reports, 1981 (Box 2.189, Folder 19)
    - Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 2.19, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1984 (Box 2.19, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1985 (Box 2.19, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1986 (Box 2.19, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1987 (Box 2.19, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Programs
    - Meeting, 6-7 Dec. 1986 (Box 2.135, Folder 15)
    - Meeting, 3 Oct. 1987 (Box 2.136, Folder 1)
    - Subcommittee on Education Grants, 1996-1997 (Box 2.136, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Publications
    - Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2.136, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 2.136, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2.136, Folder 5)
    - General, 1954 (Box 2.19, Folder 6)
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.136, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 3 Feb. 1988 (Box 2.136, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 1 Feb. 1989 (Box 2.19, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 1 Feb. 1989 (Box 2.136, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 1 Feb. 1989 (Box 2.136, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 3 Oct. 1992 (Box 2.136, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 13 Jul. 1994 (Box 2.136, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 13 Jul. 1994 (Box 2.137, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 13 Jul. 1994 (Box 2.137, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 11 Dec. 2000 (Box 2.137, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 2.137, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1988 (Box 2.137, Folder 5)
    - Response, 1992 (Box 2.137, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Qualifications
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1991-1992 (Box 2.137, Folder 7)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1992-1993 (Box 2.137, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1992-1993 (Box 2.137, Folder 9)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1993-1994 (Box 2.137, Folder 10)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1994-1995 (Box 2.137, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1995-1996 (Box 2.138, Folder 1)
    - Certificate of Excellence, 1996-1997 (Box 2.138, Folder 2)
    - Certificate of Excellence: University of Michigan, 1991-1992 (Box 2.138, Folder 3)
    - Certificate of Excellence: University of Michigan, 1991-1992 (Box 2.138, Folder 4)
    - Chapter/Club Officers' Handbook, 1994-1995 (Box 2.138, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Information, 1995-1997 (Box 2.138, Folder 6)
    - Chapter Information, 1995-1997 (Box 2.138, Folder 7)
    - Chapter Information, 1995-1997 (Box 2.139, Folder 1)
    - Committee Service, 1994-1996 (Box 2.139, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2.139, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2.139, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2.139, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2.139, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2.139, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 2.139, Folder 8)
    - General, 1973 (Box 2.19, Folder 8)
    - General, 1974 (Box 2.19, Folder 9)
    - General, 1975 (Box 2.19, Folder 10)
    - General, 1975-1984 (Box 2.14, Folder 1)
    - General, 1976 (Box 2.19, Folder 11)
    - General, 1977 (Box 2.19, Folder 12)
    - General, 1978 (Box 2.19, Folder 13)
    - General, 1979 (Box 2.19, Folder 14)
    - General, 1980-1982 (Box 2.19, Folder 15)
    - General, 1983 (Box 2.19, Folder 16)
    - General, 1984 (Box 2.19, Folder 17)
    - General, 1984 (Box 2.14, Folder 2)
    - General, 1985 (Box 2.14, Folder 3)
    - General, 1985 (Box 2.14, Folder 4)
    - General, 1986 (Box 2.14, Folder 5)
    - General, 1986 (Box 2.14, Folder 6)
    - General, 1987 (Box 2.14, Folder 7)
    - General, 1987 (Box 2.141, Folder 1)
    - General, 1988 (Box 2.141, Folder 2)
    - General, 1989 (Box 2.141, Folder 3)
    - General, 1990 (Box 2.141, Folder 4)
    - General, 1990 (Box 2.141, Folder 5)
    - General, 1990-1992 (Box 2.141, Folder 6)
    - General, 1991 (Box 2.141, Folder 7)
    - General, 1991 (Box 2.141, Folder 8)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.142, Folder 1)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.142, Folder 2)
    - General, 1993-1994 (Box 2.142, Folder 3)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.142, Folder 4)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.142, Folder 5)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.142, Folder 6)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.142, Folder 7)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.142, Folder 8)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.142, Folder 9)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.143, Folder 1)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.143, Folder 2)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.143, Folder 3)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.143, Folder 4)
    - Job Duties, 1993 (Box 2.19, Folder 18)
    - Lucknow (India) Club, 1980-1989 (Box 2.143, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 23 Apr. 1987 (Box 2.143, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 31 Jul. 1987 (Box 2.143, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 16 Oct. 1987 (Box 2.143, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 18 Feb. 1988 (Box 2.144, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 14 Apr. 1988 (Box 2.144, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 16-18 Sep. 1988 (Box 2.144, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 13-15 Oct. 1989 (Box 2.144, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 20-21 Oct. 1990 (Box 2.144, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 10 Mar. 1991 (Box 2.144, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 1 Nov. 1994 (Box 2.144, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 20-22 Jan. 1995 (Box 2.144, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 21-22 Jan. 1995 (Box 2.144, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 20-21 Jan. 1996 (Box 2.144, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 20-21 Jan. 1996 (Box 2.144, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 20-21 Jan. 1996 (Box 2.144, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, Sep. 1997 (Box 2.144, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, 1999 (Box 2.144, Folder 14)
    - Meeting, 31 Mar. - 2 Apr. 2000 (Box 2.145, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 8-10 Jun. 2001 (Box 2.145, Folder 2)
    - Response, 1992 (Box 2.145, Folder 3)
    - Surveys, 1983-1984 (Box 2.145, Folder 4)
    - Surveys, 1986-1990 (Box 2.145, Folder 5)
    - Surveys, 1994 (Box 2.145, Folder 6)
    - Trip Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 2.145, Folder 7)
    - Trip Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 2.145, Folder 8)
    - Trip Reports, 1987-1990 (Box 2.145, Folder 9)
    - Trip Reports, 1991 (Box 2.145, Folder 10)
    - Trip Reports, 1991 (Box 2.146, Folder 1)
    - Trip Reports, 1992 (Box 2.146, Folder 2)
    - Trip Reports, 1994 (Box 2.146, Folder 3)
    - Trip Reports: Special Project, 1994 (Box 2.146, Folder 4)
    - Trip Reports: Special Project, 1994 (Box 2.146, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Regions
    - General, 1973 (Box 2.19, Folder 19)
    - General, 1973 (Box 2.19, Folder 20)
    - General, 1973-1974 (Box 2.191, Folder 1)
    - General, 1979-1984 (Box 2.146, Folder 6)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 2.191, Folder 2)
    - General, 1983-1984 (Box 2.191, Folder 3)
    - General, 1988 (Box 2.146, Folder 7)
    - General, 1991-1992 (Box 2.146, Folder 8)
    - General, 1991 (Box 2.146, Folder 9)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.146, Folder 10)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.146, Folder 11)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.146, Folder 12)
    - General, 1994-1995 (Box 2.147, Folder 1)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.147, Folder 2)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.147, Folder 3)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.147, Folder 4)
    - General, 1997-1998 (Box 2.147, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 24 Apr. 1987 (Box 2.147, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 16-19 Oct. 1987 (Box 2.147, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 15 Apr. 1988 (Box 2.147, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 27-30 Oct. 1988 (Box 2.147, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 15-17 Apr. 1994 (Box 2.147, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 12 Jan. 1996 (Box 2.147, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 1996 (Box 2.148, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 18-20 Sep. 1998 (Box 2.148, Folder 2)
    - Mid-Atlantic Region, 1979-1981 (Box 2.191, Folder 4)
    - Mid-Atlantic Region, 1981-1984 (Box 2.191, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 2.148, Folder 3)
    - North Central Region, 1973-1977 (Box 2.191, Folder 6)
    - Northeast Region, 1979-1980 (Box 2.191, Folder 7)
    - Northeast Region, 1996 (Box 2.148, Folder 4)
    - Northwest Region, 1979-1984 (Box 2.191, Folder 8)
    - Reports for the Assembly of Delegates, 1993 (Box 2.148, Folder 5)
    - Southeast Region, 1979-1984 (Box 2.191, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Region, 1979-1983 (Box 2.191, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Science and Society
    - Animals in Research, 1990 (Box 2.148, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1978-1992 (Box 2.148, Folder 7)
    - Applicant Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2.148, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Freedom of Information, National Prosperity, and International Security, 1990 (Box 2.148, Folder 9)
    - Committee Members, 1990-1994 (Box 2.148, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2.148, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2.148, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2.191, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2.148, Folder 13)
    - Edinburgh Science Festival, 1991 (Box 2.148, Folder 14)
    - Expenditures, 1981-1988 (Box 2.148, Folder 15)
    - General, 1985 (Box 2.191, Folder 12)
    - General, 1985 (Box 2.191, Folder 13)
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box 2.148, Folder 16)
    - General, 1990 (Box 2.148, Folder 17)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.148, Folder 18)
    - Grant Application Forms, undated (Box 2.148, Folder 19)
    - Grant Applications, 1977-1978 (Box 2.148, Folder 20)
    - Grant Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 2.149, Folder 1)
    - Grant Applications, 1979-1980 (Box 2.149, Folder 2)
    - Grant Applications, 1980-1981 (Box 2.149, Folder 3)
    - Grant Applications, 1981-1982 (Box 2.149, Folder 4)
    - Grant Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 2.149, Folder 5)
    - Grant Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 2.149, Folder 6)
    - Grant Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 2.149, Folder 7)
    - Grant Applications, 1988-1989 (Box 2.149, Folder 8)
    - Grant Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 2.149, Folder 9)
    - Grant Applications, 1990-1991 (Box 2.15, Folder 1)
    - Grant Applications, 1991-1992 (Box 2.15, Folder 2)
    - Grant Applications, 1992-1993 (Box 2.15, Folder 3)
    - Ideas For Issues, 1994 (Box 2.15, Folder 4)
    - McGowan, Alan and Jerry Eberhart, 1990 (Box 2.191, Folder 14)
    - McGowan, Alan, May 1991 - 30 Jun. 1992 (Box 2.191, Folder 15)
    - Meeting, 6-8 Jun. 1986 (Box 2.15, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 21 Nov. 1986 (Box 2.15, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 27-28 Jun. 1987 (Box 2.15, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 17 Oct. 1987 (Box 2.15, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 17-18 Jun. 1988 (Box 2.15, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 17-18 Jun. 1988 (Box 2.15, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 27 Oct. 1988 (Box 2.151, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 5-6 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.151, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 5-6 Mar. 1989 (Box 2.151, Folder 3)